Guide to the Students for Choice records, 1983-2003 UA.31.08.0007
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Students for Choice records
1983-2003
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Students for Choice
UA.31.08.0007
0.5 Linear Feet
Students for Choice is a student organization dedicated to educating the Duke community about the status of reproductive rights nationally and locally and about available related resources, and to working to protect and uphold the freedom of choice. The Students for Choice Records contains flyers and other event materials, organizational notes, educational literature, and clippings.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for access.
Historical Note
Students for Choice is a student organization dedicated to educating the Duke community about the status of reproductive rights nationally and locally and about available related resources, and to working to protect and uphold the freedom of choice.
Collection Overview
The Students for Choice Records contains flyers and other event materials, organizational notes, educational literature, and clippings.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Students for Choice records were received by the Duke University Archives as a gift in 2008.
Pro-choice movement -- North Carolina; Women's rights; Student activism; Students for Choice; Duke University -- Students
- Administrative notes, correspondence, and sign-up sheets, 1996-2003 (Box 1)
- Flyers, 1996 and undated (Box 1)
- National Young Women's Day of Action, 2000 October 25 (Box 1)
- Election and political candidate information, 2000 (Box 1)
- Campus for Choice: Organizing a Campus for Choice Group, circa 1990s (Box 1)
- Fact Sheets, 1998, 2000 (Box 1)
- Pro-Choice Religious Group Printed Materials, 1980s-1990s (Box 1)
- Pro-Life Printed Materials, 1980s-1990s (Box 1)
- Various National Groups Printed Materials, 1980s-1990s (Box 1)
- Clippings: Time Magazine and the News & Observer, 1983, 1997 (Box 1)